https://www.paulaschmitt.com/privacy-policy-2/

Skip to content
Your privacy is important to us. It is PaulaSchmitt.com’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://www.paulaschmitt.com, and other sites we own and operate.
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
This policy is effective as of 15 January 2020.
Generated by GetTerms.io
Search for:
Popular Posts
Tips For Using Property Management Pensacola Services To Your Advantage
March 4, 2020
There are numerous people who own tracts of land that they allow other individuals to use for a certain price, but not all property owners know the advantages of availing property management services to assist them with the issues that can arise. Most individuals think about purchasing lots to let
Banner Stands Options To Choose From
February 25, 2020February 25, 2020
Drive More Website Traffic With An SEO Company As Your Partner
Tips For Using Property Management Pensacola Services To Your Advantage
Tips For Using Property Management Pensacola Services To Your Advantage
March 4, 2020
Banner Stands Options To Choose From
February 25, 2020February 25, 2020
Drive More Website Traffic With An SEO Company As Your Partner
January 28, 2020
About Us
PaulaSchmitt.com is your portal to news and info on business, finance, real estate, and technology topics that influence our lives.
Most Viewed Posts
